Full Stack Developer

Professional Summary

An independent and self-motivated student with proven ability and experience in Investment Audits and Global Audit Methodology(GAM). I have also participated in various trainings conducted by the organization which helped me in better communication, team work, quality and timely project completion.

Experience

2022-07 -Current

Intern - Fullstack Developer

Refactor, Bengaluru, Karnataka

- Full stack development along with problem solving training
- Evaluated the structure and design of web pages
- Used best practise in HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP, JAVASCRIPT, REACTJS to develop a dynamic state.
- Learned font-end object-oriented programming to develop a responsive website.
- Efficient with popular work environment like Visual Studio and Brackets.

2016-08 -2018-02

Advanced Audit Associate

EY Global Services, Bangalore, Krnataka

- Performed Lead Tie outs, Roll Forwarding of Prior Yera Documents, Financial Tie Outs, SOX Audit.
- Extensive working experience on EY Canvas and Sharepoint.
- worked extensively on windows environment with IBM notes Application.
- Communicating with Clients to determine specific requirements and expectations. Managing client expectations as an indicator of quality
- Ensuring the maintenance of positive and on-going relations with clients.
- Ensuring the quality of my junior staffs trainings and their work.

2016-01 -2016-06

Process Associate

Genpact India Ltd, Hyderabad, Telangana

- Worked on Purchase Cards Limit for Universal Studios
- Worked on Bills Receivables and Payables
- Worked on Ledger Maintenance

Contact

City

Kakinada, Andhra Pradesh, India, 533016

Phone 9966625512

E-mail

krishnakishoresamanchi@gmai l.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/s amanchi-kishore-1b8593111/

Github Link

https://github.com/Samanchi

Languages & Frameworks

HTML

CSS

BOOTSTRAP

JavaScript

ReactJS

NodeJS

Python

Object Oriented Programming

Education

DEGREE :BCOM (Comp)

2012-07 - 2015-08

Adikavi Nannaya University Kakinada - Andhra Pradesh

- Done my graduation in Finance with Accounting, Commerce, Economics and Statistics as Majors
- 60%

12th: Board of Intermediate Education

2010-05 - 2012-04

Narayana Junior College Kakinada - Andhra Pradesh

- Done my PUC in Accounts with Accounts, Economics and maths as majors
- 87%

CALCULATOR APP

- Deevloped a basic Calculator application using HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, REACT..
- Considered UseState Hooks to create application in react.
- User can perform all sorts of Airthmetic Operations using this application.

TIC-TAC-TOE GAME APP

- Developed a basic tic-tac-toe game using HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT.
- Developed in a responsive way to make user experience better.

PORTFOLIO WEBSITE

- Developed a website where users can check my complete profile.
- User has to SignUp into the site to view the profile if he/she is accessing for the first time. Else they can view it by SignIn info.
- User can send Mails through GMAIL by entering their mailId and message.
- Users can send Message directly on Whatsapp.
- Employers can download my Resume through site directly.

10th: Board of Secondary and Higher Education

2009-04 - 2010-03 Aditya Public School Kakinada - Andhra Pradesh • 83%

Strenghts

Positive Attitude

Adaptability & Flexibility

Enthusiam for Learning

Communication

Team Management

Time Managament

Interests

Sports

Analysis

New Languages

Project Management